Finding Aid for the Paul D. Boyer Papers, 1943-2009 LSC.2156
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Academia, 1941-2008; 1960-1993
  - Subseries 1.3: Conferences, 1967-2005; 1970-2002
    - Conferences: U Penn "NMR and Biochemistry Symposium in honor of Mildred Cohn", "Oxygen Exchange Approaches to the Mechanism of Pyrophosphatase, Oxidative Phosphorylation, and Actomyosin ATPase"., 1978 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      NMR - Nuclear Magnetic Resonance
    - Conferences: U of Southern California seminar, 1978. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Conferences: ASBC conference, 1979., 1978 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Conferences: Baylor College seminar, 1979. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Conferences: 6th Enzyme Mechanisms Conference, 1979. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Conferences: 11th International Congress of Biochemistry, "Protein Conformational Changes in Energy Transduction"., 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Conferences: Oregon State U, 14th Annual Pauling Award honoring Daniel Koshland, 1979. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Conferences: South African Biochemical Society meeting, 1979., 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Conferences: UCLA symposium in honor of E.L. Smith, 1979., 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Conferences: U of Georgia seminar, 1979., 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Conferences: USC seminar, 1979. (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Conferences: U of Texas Distinguished Faculty seminar, 1979. (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Conferences: Wayne State U, "Membrane Bioenergetics" July 1979. (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Conferences: ACS Symposium, 1980. (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Conferences: CSU Northridge seminar, 1980. (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Conferences: 1st European Bioenergetics Conference., 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Conferences: 3rd International Symposium on Na, K-ATPase, 1980. (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Conferences: Plato Society Lecture, 1980. (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Conferences: U of Victoria seminar, 1980. (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Conferences: CSU Fullerton seminar, "Catalysis in Biological Energy Transductions", 1981. (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Conferences: GRC Aug. 17-21, 1981 "Energy Coupling Mechanisms". (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Conferences: Guelph-Waterloo Distinguished Lecturer, 1981. (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Conferences: Lighthouse Conference, 1981. (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Conferences: MBI Asilomar, 1981. (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Conferences: New Mexico University seminar, 1981. (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Conferences: 11th Steenbock Symposium, "An Evaluation of the Present Status of the Binding change Mechanism for ATP Formation by Chloroplasts" lecture, 1981., 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Conferences: UC Berkeley/UC Santa Cruz seminar, November 1981. (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Conferences: UC Riverside seminar, 1981. (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Conferences: UC San Francisco seminar, "Enzyme Mechanisms in Biological Energy Transductions", 1981. (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Conferences: West Central States Biochemical, 1981. (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Conferences: ASBC New Orleans, 1982. (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Conferences: 2nd European Bioenergetics Conference., 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Conferences: Margaret J. Hastings Distinguished Lectures in Biochemistry, 1982. (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Conferences: New York Academy of Sciences Meeting (Transport ATPases Conference)., 1982 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Conferences: Steenbock-Lilly Symposium for Henry Lardy, 1982., 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Conferences: UCLA, 57th Faculty Research Lecture, "How Living Cells Use Energy", 1982., 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Conferences: Biophysical Society Meetings, 1983-1984. (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Conferences: Boyer Symposium, "Enzyme Catalysis and Control"., 1983 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Conferences: 8th Enzymes Mechanisms Conference., 1983 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Conferences: GRC July 4-8, 1983 "Enzymes, Coenzymes, and Metabolic Pathways". (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Conferences: GRC Aug. 15-19, 1983 "Energy Coupling Mechanisms"., 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Conferences: International Workshop on H+-ATPase, "Correlations of the Binding Change Mechanism with a New Concept for Protein Translocation and Energy Transmission"., 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Conferences: 13th Steenbock Symposium, "100 years of agricultural chemistry and biochemistry", 1983. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Conferences: ASBC Anaheim meeting, 1984. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Conferences: 3rd European Bioenergetics Conference., 1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Conferences: 16th FEBS meeting, "Energy-linked Changes of Enzyme Conformation in ATP Formation and Use"., 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Conferences: 16th FEBS meeting and 2nd International Symposium on "Frontiers of Bioorganic Chemistry and Molecular Biology", 1984. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Conferences: GRC Aug. 19-24, 1984 "Photosynthesis". (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Conferences: International Symposium on Frontiers in Bio-Organic chemistry and Molecular Biology in Moscow-Alma Ata, 1984. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Conferences: International Workshop on the Mechanism of Action of H+-ATPase synthase, 1984. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Conferences: IUB H+-ATPase Synthase Symposium, 1984., circa 1984 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      IUB (later IUBMB) - International Union of Biochemistry
    - Conferences: PAABS Conference, 1984., 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      PAABS - Pan-American Association of Biochemical Societies.
    - Conferences: UCB seminar, 1984. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Conferences: 11th Yamada Conference on Energy Transduction in ATPases (declined)., 1984 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Conferences: GRC Jan. 28-Feb. 1, 1985 "Protons and Membrane Reactions"., 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Conferences: GRC July 1-5, 1985 "Energy Coupling Mechanisms"., 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Conferences: International Symposium in South Africa, "Membranes and Muscles", 1985., 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Conferences: Michigan State Upjohn Lecture, "The Remarkable Enzymology of ATP Synthase", 1985. (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Conferences: Simon Fraser University, Seelochan Beharry thesis defense., 1985 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Conferences: University of Southern California seminar, 1985. (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Conferences: Albert Lehninger Memorial Symposium ("The Mitochondrion")., 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Conferences: Biophysical Society Meeting, 1986., 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Conferences: 4th European Bioenergetics Conference., 1986 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Conferences: NIGMS Symposium at NAGMS council meeting., 1986 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      NIGMS - National Institute of General Medical Sciences
      NAGMS - National Advisory General Medical Sciences
    - Conferences: Stanford Visiting Scholar Seminar Program, October 1986. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Conferences: State University of New York Upstate Medical University, 1986. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Conferences: ASBC, 1987. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Conferences: GRC June 28-July 3, 1987 "Energy Coupling Mechanisms"., 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Conferences: 5th European Bioenergetics Conference., 1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Conferences: U of Wisconsin seminar, 1988. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Conferences: GRC July 24-28, 1989 "Bioenergetics" (formerly "Energy Coupling Mechanisms"). (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Conferences: 6th European Bioenergetics Conference., 1990 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Conferences: U of Padua, symposium in honor of Prof. Siliprandi, 1990., 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Conferences: 19th Aharon Katzir-Katchalsky, 1991., 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Conferences: GRC July 8-12, 1991 "Bioenergetics". (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Conferences: IUB, 15th International Congress of Biochemistry, 1991., 1988-1991 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Conferences: ASBMB abstracts, 1992., 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Conferences: NIH Symposium, 1991., 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Conferences: U of Oregon, 1992. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Conferences: U Penn, 10th Mildred Cohn Lecture, 1992. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Conferences: AMBO Training Course, 1993., 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      AMBO - Asian Molecular Biology Organization
    - Conferences: ASU seminar, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Conferences: Scripps Research Institute seminar, 1993., 1992 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Conferences: GRC Jan. 30-Feb. 4, 1994 "Protons & Membrane Reactions". (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Conferences: International Symposium on "Thirty Years of Progress in Mitochondrial Bioenergetics and Molecular Biology", 1994., 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Conferences: GRC Feb. 23-28, 1997, "Protons and Membrane Reactions"., 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Conferences: ASBMB Fall Symposium on Phosphoryl Transfer at Lake Tahoe, 1998. (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Conferences: Caltech seminar, 1998. (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Conferences: Cal State Fullerton seminar, 1988 + 1998. (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Conferences: Cal State Northridge, Biology Colloquium Series, 1998. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Conferences: 10th European Bioenergetics, 1998., 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Conferences: Encino-Tarzana Regional Medical Center participation., 1998 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Conferences: Jichi Medical School, Symposium on Bioenergetics and ATP synthase, 1998. (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Conferences: Lindau Nobel Laureates meeting, 1998., 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Conferences: National Academy of Sciences, public symposium at UC Irvine., 1998 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Conferences: Syracuse U, The Charles R. Ross Research lecture, 1998. (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Conferences: UCLA Alumni Associations "UC Day in Sacramento"., 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Conferences: U Michigan Biochemistry Colloquium, 1998., 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Conferences: Cal State Long Beach, Nobel Laureate Lecture Series, 1999., 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Conferences: ACS Southern California Section, "Chemistry into the New Millenium", 2000. (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Conferences: Burnham Institute seminar, 2000. (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Conferences: Clemson U seminar, 2000., 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Conferences: 15th FAOBMB Symposium, 2000. (Box 18, Folder 41)
      FAOBMB - Federation of Asian and Oceanian Biochemists and Molecular Biologists
    - Conferences: GRC Feb. 20-25, 2000 "Protons and Membrane Reactions"., 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Conferences: Lindau Nobel Laureate Meetings, 2000. (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Conferences: Ralph and Helen Oesper Symposium honoring Mildren Cohen, 2000., 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Conferences: Science and Technology of Thailand (STT) annual meeting, 2000., 1998-2001 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Conferences: UCB Daniel I. Arnon lecture, 2000., 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Conferences: Nobel Centennial and Youth Science Symposiums, 2001., 1999-2001 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Conferences: Cal State LA seminar, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Conferences: Lindau Nobel Laureates Meeting, 2002., 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Conferences: Milken Institute Global Conference, 2002., 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Conferences: UN World Summit for Sustainable Development, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Conferences: U Michigan, a symposium on cellular oxidation in honor of Donald E. Hultquist, 2002., 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Conferences: U of Stockholm, The Lars Ernster Lecture on Bioenergetics, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Conferences: ACS Meeting, March 2003., 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Conferences: Amgen seminar, 2003., 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Conferences: Kansas University, Newmark Award Lectures, 2003. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Conferences: Lindau Nobel Laureates meeting, 2005., 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Conferences: misc. conference materials., 1944-1998 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      Contains travel itineraries/receipts, conference schedules, and invitations to various conferences. Materials were found stuck in the space between two flanking folders.
  - Subseries 1.4: Professional Societies, 1955-2008; 1965-1995
    This subseries contains information relating to Boyer's leadership and membership positions in the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, American Chemical Society (ACS), American Society of Biological Chemists (ASBC), as well as the National Academy of Science (NAS). It also contains correspondence about his editorial work on the 18-volume treatise The Enzymes and with the "Recollections" section of Protein Science.
    General note
    ACS - American Chemical Society
    ASBC/ASBMB - the American Society of Biological Chemists (ASBC) underwent a name change in 1987 to the American Society of Biochemistry and Molecular Biology (ASBMB)
    FASEB – Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology
    PNAS - Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences
    NAS – National Academy of Sciences
    NIH - National Institutes of Health
    NSF - National Science Foundation
    - Editorial Boards: "The Enzymes" correspondence., 1987-2008 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Editorial Boards: Protein Science Recollections correspondence., 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Editorial Boards: Protein Science Recollections correspondence., 1994-1996 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Editorial Boards: Protein Science Recollections, Neurath correspondence., 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Editorial Boards: Protein Science Recollections, Neurath correspondence (1 of 2)., 1993-1997 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Editorial Boards: Protein Science Recollections, Neurath correspondence (2 of 2)., 1993-1997 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Editorial Boards: Protein Science Recollections, coordinator reports & related., 1993-1996 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Editorial Boards: Protein Science Recollections, response to 1995 invitations., 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Professional Societies: American Academy of Arts & Sciences, membership & nominations., 1968, 1998-2007 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Professional Societies: American Academy of Arts and Sciences, resignation from Class II Membership Committee VP., 1987 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Professional Societies: American Academy of Arts and Sciences Committee, Grobstein Correspondence., 1993 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Professional Societies: ACS, Minnesota section., 1955-1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Professional Societies: ACS Chairman's File, 1959-1960. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Professional Societies: ACS Biological Chemistry Division., 1963, 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Professional Societies: ACS Satellite TV Seminars, "Transferring the Energy of Life"., 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Professional Societies: ACS High School Day, 1999., 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Professional Societies: American Philosophical Society, Membership Election., 1998 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Professional Societies: American Philosophical Society (APS)., 1998-2007 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Professional Societies: ASBC, Public Affairs Advisory Committee, 1986. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Professional Societies: ASBC Presidency 1968-1969. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Professional Societies: ASBC Presidency papers (1 of 2)., 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Professional Societies: ASBC Presidency papers (2 of 2)., 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Professional Societies: ASBC Public Policy Committee, 1970-1971. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Professional Societies: ASBC, Boyer's congressional testimony to the House Subcommittee on Appropriations for Labor and Welfare., 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Professional Societies: ASBC, Public Affairs Advisory Committee, 1983. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Professional Societies: ASBC, Public Affairs Advisory Committee on subject of indirect costs., 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Professional Societies: ASBC, Public Affairs Advisory Committee, 1984-1985. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Professional Societies: ASBC, regarding public perception of biotech and its legislation., 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Professional Societies: ASBC, Public Affairs Advisory Committee, 1987 (1 of 2). (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Professional Societies: ASBC, Public Affairs Advisory Committee, 1987 (2 of 2). (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Professional Societies: ASBC, drafts of letter in response to environmental groups., 1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Professional Societies: ASBMB correspondence., 1969, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Professional Societies: Federation of American Scientists (FAS) on nuclear arms control., 2000-2003 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Professional Societies: FASEB Public Affairs Committee., 1984-1987 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Professional Societies: FASEB, ASBMB on subject of indirect costs (1 of 2)., 1986-1992 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Professional Societies: FASEB, ASBMB on subject of indirect costs (2 of 2)., 1986-1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Professional Societies: NAS, PNAS forms & notices., 1996-2004 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Professional Societies: NAS, Chen et al. manuscript review for PNAS., 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Professional Societies: NAS membership elections., 2004-2007 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Professional Societies: NAS, committee election forms., 1973-1986, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Professional Societies: NIH, Biochemistry Study Section Chairmanship., 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Professional Societies: NIH, study section meeting, January 1966. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Professional Societies: NIH, study section meeting, April 1966. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Professional Societies: NIH, study section chairmen meeting, August 1966. (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Professional Societies: NIH, study section meeting, September 1966. (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Professional Societies: NIH, study section meeting, January 1967. (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Professional Societies: NIH, study section meeting, May 1967. (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Professional Societies: Regarding future of the Journal of Biological Chemistry., 1975-1986 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Professional Societies: Response to House Subcommittee on Appropriations for Labor and Welfare., 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Professional Societies: Union of Concerned Scientists., 2004 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Reviews: Book Reviews, Manuscripts, Grants (1 of 2)., 1966-1976 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Reviews: Book Reviews, Manuscripts, Grants (2 of 2)., 1966-1976, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      Contains some review index cards dated around 1985. These cards were likely not in the folder originally and were found without context.
    - Reviews: NSF Proposal Ratings, 1967-1973. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Reviews: NSF Proposal Ratings, 1974-1977. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Reviews: NSF Proposal Ratings, 1977-1997. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Reviews: The Energy of Life by Guy Brown., 2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Reviews: Menz, Walker, and Leslie manuscript, "Crystal structure of bovine mitochondrial F1-ATPase"., 2001 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 1.5: UCLA, 1974-2009; 1977-1990
    This subseries has material related to Boyer's involvement in various UCLA projects, ranging from a proposed bikeway (the WestLA Veloway) to the creation and leadership of the Molecular Biology Institute (MBI). 2 folders pertaining to the attempted establishment of UC-affiliated companies that would profit off of university research are also available, as are folders containing materials about joint research projects between UCLA and the US Department of Energy such as the Laboratory of Structural Biology and Molecular Medicine (LSBMM).
    - WestLA Veloway: Bicycle Freeway., 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - WestLA Veloway: Bicycle Transportation (1 of 4)., 1979-1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - WestLA Veloway: Bicycle Transportation (2 of 4)., 1979-1982 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - WestLA Veloway: Bicycle Transportation (3 of 4)., 1979-1982 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - WestLA Veloway: Bicycle Transportation (4 of 4)., 1979-1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - WestLA Veloway: Bicycle Feasibility study, 1974. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - WestLA Veloway: Endorsements, requests for funding, and press., 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - WestLA Veloway: misc. correspondence and press (1 of 4)., 1977-2000 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - WestLA Veloway: misc. correspondence and press (2 of 4)., 1977-2000 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - WestLA Veloway: misc. correspondence and press (3 of 4)., 1977-2000 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - WestLA Veloway: misc. correspondence and press (4 of 4)., 1977-2000 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - WestLA Veloway: misc. reports and plans., 1977-1990 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - WestLA Veloway: Reports and proposals., 1974-1990 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - WestLA Veloway: Veloway Foundation Inquiries for Funding., 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - WestLA Veloway: Veloway Material Record from Dave, Fall 1984. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - WestLA Veloway: UCLA Lot 1 Development Final Environmental Impact Report., 1986 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - WestLA Veloway: List of project supporters., 1980s (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - WestLA Veloway: Summary Report and Feasibility Study., circa 1984 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI, Annual Newsletters No. 43, 44., 2007-2008 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI, historical publications by Richard Dickerson., 2006-2009 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      Contains copies of Ars Gratia Scientia (2006) and The Making of an Institute (2009), booklets by Dickerson relaying the history of the MBI.
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI retreat at Lake Arrowhead, 1987. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI retreat at Lake Arrowhead, 1997. (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI retreat at Lake Arrowhead, 40th Anniversary., 2005 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI, Systemwide Biotechnology Research and Education Program, administrative matters., 1986-1991 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI, Systemwide Biotechnology Research and Education Program, appointments and promotions of Susanne Huttner., 1985-1988 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI, Systemwide Biotechnology Research and Education Program, advisory committee., 1985-1987 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI, Systemwide Biotechnology Research and Education Program, Biotechnology in US-Pacific Relations Conference., 1988 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI, Systemwide Biotechnology Research and Education Program, budget related., 1986-1988 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI, Systemwide Biotechnology Research and Education Program, executive committee., 1985-1994 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI, Systemwide Biotechnology Research and Education Program, increasing public awareness/education of biotechnology., 1986-1990 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI, Systemwide Biotechnology Research and Education Program, Proposals., 1986 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI, Systemwide Biotechnology Research and Education Program, regarding biotechnology restrictions and regulations by the USDA and EPA., 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI, Systemwide Biotechnology Research and Education Program, requests for proposals., 1986-1988 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI, Systemwide Biotechnology Research and Education Program, summary reports (1 of 2)., 1985-1993 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - UCLA Institutes: MBI, Systemwide Biotechnology Research and Education Program, summary reports (2 of 2)., 1985-1993 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - UCLA Institutes: UCLA-DOE LSBMM Advisory Committee., 1995-1999 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      LSBMM - Lab of Structural Biology & Molecular Medicine
    - UCLA Institutes: UCLA-DOE Institute for Genomics and Proteomics., 1998-2008 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - UCLA Institutes: UCLA-DOE Institute for Genomics and Proteomics, 5 Year Review Director's Report., 2004-2009 (Box 29, Folder 3)